{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Refrigeration \u0026 Ice Machine Installation Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40307/":{"taskOID":40307,"originalTaskOID":40307,"setID":607,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6924,"questionDisplayText":"Refrigeration needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Describe the type of refrigeration system you want: (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":940,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bar","answerDisplayText":"Bar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7020,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wine cellar","answerDisplayText":"Wine cellar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3139,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Ice machine","answerDisplayText":"Ice machine","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1011,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Beer cooler","answerDisplayText":"Beer cooler","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2550,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Floral cabinet","answerDisplayText":"Floral cabinet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3110,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Humidor","answerDisplayText":"Humidor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6728,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Walk-in cooler","answerDisplayText":"Walk-in cooler","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6729,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Walk-in freezer","answerDisplayText":"Walk-in freezer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5051,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Reach-in freezer","answerDisplayText":"Reach-in freezer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1804,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Dairy cabinet","answerDisplayText":"Dairy cabinet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10114,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Display cooler","answerDisplayText":"Display cooler","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10115,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Deli cooler","answerDisplayText":"Deli cooler","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4781,"questionDisplayText":"Distance from cooler to unit","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the distance from the cooler to the refrigeration unit?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3561,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than three feet","answerDisplayText":"Less than three feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":450,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3-10 feet","answerDisplayText":"3-10 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":317,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"10-20 feet","answerDisplayText":"10-20 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3925,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 20 feet","answerDisplayText":"More than 20 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6924,"questionDisplayText":"Refrigeration needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Describe the type of refrigeration system you want: (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":940,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bar","answerDisplayText":"Bar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7020,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wine cellar","answerDisplayText":"Wine cellar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3139,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Ice machine","answerDisplayText":"Ice machine","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1011,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Beer cooler","answerDisplayText":"Beer cooler","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2550,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Floral cabinet","answerDisplayText":"Floral cabinet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3110,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Humidor","answerDisplayText":"Humidor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6728,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Walk-in cooler","answerDisplayText":"Walk-in cooler","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6729,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Walk-in freezer","answerDisplayText":"Walk-in freezer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5051,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Reach-in freezer","answerDisplayText":"Reach-in freezer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1804,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Dairy cabinet","answerDisplayText":"Dairy cabinet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10114,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Display cooler","answerDisplayText":"Display cooler","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10115,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Deli cooler","answerDisplayText":"Deli cooler","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":940,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bar","answerDisplayText":"Bar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7020,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wine cellar","answerDisplayText":"Wine cellar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3139,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Ice machine","answerDisplayText":"Ice machine","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1011,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Beer cooler","answerDisplayText":"Beer cooler","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2550,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Floral cabinet","answerDisplayText":"Floral cabinet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3110,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Humidor","answerDisplayText":"Humidor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6728,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Walk-in cooler","answerDisplayText":"Walk-in cooler","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6729,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Walk-in freezer","answerDisplayText":"Walk-in freezer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5051,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Reach-in freezer","answerDisplayText":"Reach-in freezer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1804,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Dairy cabinet","answerDisplayText":"Dairy cabinet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10114,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Display cooler","answerDisplayText":"Display cooler","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10115,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Deli cooler","answerDisplayText":"Deli cooler","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4781,"questionDisplayText":"Distance from cooler to unit","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the distance from the cooler to the refrigeration unit?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3561,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than three feet","answerDisplayText":"Less than three feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":450,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3-10 feet","answerDisplayText":"3-10 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":317,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"10-20 feet","answerDisplayText":"10-20 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3925,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 20 feet","answerDisplayText":"More than 20 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3561,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than three feet","answerDisplayText":"Less than three feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":450,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3-10 feet","answerDisplayText":"3-10 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":317,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"10-20 feet","answerDisplayText":"10-20 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3925,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 20 feet","answerDisplayText":"More than 20 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/40307/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40307,"taskName":"Refrigeration System - Install or Replace","taskDescription":"Install or Replace a Refrigeration System","xmTaskDescriptor":"Refrigeration \u0026 Ice Machine Installation Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1600,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Airconditioning ac conditioning cool units","textMessagingName":"Inst Refridg Sys","rolloverLongDesc":"These systems are used in larger, typical commercial settings.","rolloverShortDesc":"Heavy duty commercial air conditioning.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace a Refrigeration System.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Refrigeration Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install Ice Machine, Wine Cooler, etc.","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":60,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Refrigeration System Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Refrigeration System - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Refrigerator System Project","urlName":"Refrigeration-System-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Refrigeration \u0026 Ice Machine Companies - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"commercial","emcCategoryOid":-12058,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":607,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}